RAJAT KAMBLE

Nagpur, India 440012 ● +917020010474 ● rajat.kamble51@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Highly communicative Payroll Specialist promoting more than 5+ years of expertise in auditing payroll data and processing garnishments. Ability to handle multiple projects simultaneously with a high degree of accuracy.

Skills

- Communication
- Payroll Taxes
- MS Office
- Research Skill
- Customer Service

- Team Building and Motivation
- Process Mapping
- Problem-Solving
- Analytical Skills

Work History

Business Process Lead, 11/2022 to Current

Tata Consultancy Services – Nagpur

- Supporting HR sub-process payroll, and Benefits for a US client.
- Processing separations for employees under hourly/monthly wages.
- Auditing timesheets, and salary registers for employees under hourly/monthly wages.
- Updating employee confidential data in Ceridian via Excel sheet.
- Coordinating with the accounts payable team and tracking the Vendor payment status.
- Updating employees' 401k contributions and Loan deductions on the fidelity portal.
- Validating 401k contribution and loan deduction amounts with payroll register and fidelity and according to fund the amounts.
- Update SOP, Attendance register, and prepare reports required for internal audits.

Service Delivery Associate, 07/2021 to 11/2022

Accenture PVT. LTD – Mumbai

- Co-ordinate with payroll team and provide resolution to employees enquiries regarding their payslips for European countries (UK, Ireland, Romania, and Portugal...etc).
- Provide explanations to employees regarding changes in their payslips like ESPP deduction, pension, Stock taxation.., etc.

- Explain to finance the reason for the difference in GL amount.
- Payroll application ADP Global View and ADP Celergo.
- Provide training and assistance to new Team members.

Payroll Specialist, 11/2019 to 06/2021

Neeyamo Enterprise and Solution – Pune

- Process payroll for Monthly/semi-monthly Thailand payroll for 1500 employees.
- Collect inputs and prepare payroll register based on the information received from the Client.
- Cross-validate our pay register with the Vendor pay register with the help of Vlookup.
- Prepare payroll and validate reports like GL reports, Bank files, variance reports, SSO reports, PF reports...etc.
- Validate employee taxes and tax amounts borne by the employer on behalf of employees (Gross-up calculations).
- Coordinate with the IT team to implement Thailand tax logic in the payroll system to process in-house payroll.
- Update SOP and make changes in reports with the help of the IT team as per client requirements.

Education

Bachelor Of Engineering : Electronics And Telecommunication, 2019
Gurunanak Institue of Technology - Nagpur, India

6.19 GPA/CGPA

Languages

English	Hindi
Marathi	